One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
You don't want us to open the country either.
أنتم أيضًا لا تريدون فتح هذه البلاد
Right?
صحيح؟
Because in order to fight pirates, you buy weapons from pirates.
لأنكم تريدون شراء الأسلحة من القراصنة لتقاتلوا قراصنة آخرين
Don't you find it strange?
...هذا غريب
Hmm?!
أليس كذلك؟
With your broker Doflamingo, also known as Joker, out of the picture,
بعد اعتقال وسيطكم دوفلامينغو الملقب بالجوكر
you have no choice but to trade with us directly.
فقدتم الستار الذي تختبئون خلفه واضطررتم إلى التفاوض معي مباشرة
I know you're out on a limb, so the advantage is mine...
أنتم في موقف يائس، وأنا فقط أحاول الحصول على أفضل صفقة
And already your demands are unreasonable.
مع ذلك، أنت تطلب منا الكثير
Look, Wano is entirely self-sufficient!
بلاد وانو مكتفية ذاتيًّا
Everyone here seems happy, right?
ألا ترون مدى سعادة سكان البلاد؟
If there is something we need, that would be greater power!
إن كنت أحتاج منكم شيئًا، فهو مزيد من مواضع القوة
This time, I'm only asking for a warship...
طلبي هذه المرة سفينة حربية فقط
Next time, I'll want Dr. Vegapunk!
ولكن في المرة القادمة، سيكون الدكتور فيغابانك
That's impossible!
هذا مستحيل
I didn't ask if it's possible!
لم أسألك عن استحالة طلبي من عدمه
The Celestial Dragons? The Marines?
التنانين السماوية؟ البحرية؟
You know we're not afraid of them, right?
أنتم تعرفون حق المعرفة أننا لا نخشاهم، صحيح؟
You couldn't bring us down even if you all banded together.
لا يمكنكم إسقاط هذه البلاد حتى لو اجتمعت كل قواتكم
I have Kaido backing me after all!
فأنا لدي كايدو يدعمني
Oiran Komurasaki Arrives
وصول الأويران كوموراساكي
Komurasaki the top oiran is in procession!
افسحوا الطريق لموكب المحظية المرموقة كوموراساكي
Oh, Lady Komuraski!
كوموراساكي-ساما
Look over here, Oiran!
انظري إلينا أيتها الأويران
I'm sorry I'm late!
اعذري تأخري
I was worried about you.
قلقت عليكِ
Please forgive me, Big Sis!
اعذريني يا أختاه
Now, get to work.
باشري العمل
Okay!
حاضرة
Here comes Lady Komurasaki!
ها قد أتت كوموراساكي-ساما
It's the oiran's procession!
إنه موكب الأويران
Isn't she here yet?!
ألم تصل بعد؟
There're tons of people here.
يا له من جمعٍ كبير
I wonder how beautiful she is!
ما مدى جمالها يا تُرى؟
Please hurry, Komurasaki my beloved!
أسرعي يا كوموراساكي-تشوان
That conniving tramp...
...أكره... تلك المرأة
...Komurasaki!
...كوموراساكي
I think they're looking for trouble!
يبدو أنهم ينوون افتعال مشكلة
H-Hey!
مـ-مهلًا
I've got to...
...لأقتلنّ
kill that bitch!
تلك المرأة
It's all over!
انتهى أمري
If I'm gonna die,
...إن كنتُ سأموت
I'll take her with me!
فسآخذها معي
Stay away from the oiran!
لا تعترضوا موكب الأويران
Komurasaki...
...كوموراساكي
I want to be with you forever, my love...
أريد البقاء معك إلى الأبد
W-With an old geezer like me?!
تريدين البقاء مع عجوز مثلي؟
If I have to live Shogun Orochi's puppet...
إن كنتُ سأعيش جارية لأوروتشي-ساما
I would rather you bought out my contract...
فأُفضل أن تشتري عقدي
Alas, the price for my freedom is so outrageous,
ولكن مبلغ عتقي باهظ الثمن
Imagine if Shogun Orochi were to catch wind of this conversation.
...إن عرف أوروتشي-ساما بما أخبرتك الآن، فحينها
Don't fret, my dear!
لا تفقدي الأمل
If that is your desire,
إن كانت هذه رغبتك
I, Bingo, will make it happen!
أقسم أنا بينغو بتحقيقها لك
Really?
حقًّا؟
I'm glad to hear it, even if you're not serious.
حتى لو كنت تكذب، فقد أسعدتني
You don't have enough money to pay me back?!
لا تملكان مالًا يكفي لتسديد دينكما؟
I'm sorry!
سامحنا
Do you take me for a fool?!
هل أبدو لكما غبيًّا؟
You think crying will help?!
أتظنان أنّ البكاء سيجعلني أسامحكما؟
I'll take your house as collateral for the loan!
سآخذ منزلكما بدل المال
Here, Komurasaki.
تفضلي يا كوموراساكي
I've never seen so much money!
لم أرَ مبلغًا ضخمًا كهذا قط-أرينسو
Komurasaki, here's an advance to buy you from the pleasure hall.
كوموراساكي، هذه دفعة مسبقة لعتقك من منطقة الملذات
It's not enough yet, but I want you to hold onto it.
أعلم أنها ليست كافية، ولكن احتفظي بها
Then, let me enter it in the ledger.
إذًا فلنوثّق هذه الدفعة دينًا بيننا
That's not necessary!
لا داعي لذلك
Only a fool mistrusts the woman he loves.
فقط الحمقى لا يثقون فيمن يحبونها
Your word is good enough for me.
وعدك يكفيني
My lord Bingo...
...بينغو-ساما
I cannot wait for the moment you take me with you.
لا يسعني انتظار اليوم الذي تأخذني فيه معك
Don't cry.
لا تبكي
It's all right!
لا بأس
I'll make the funeral arrangements.
سأقيم جنازة من أجلك
I'll also lend you some money for it and for living expenses.
وسأقرضك مالًا لتغطية مصاريفها ونفقات المعيشة
Stop crying already!
كفاكِ بكاءً
You need to pay me back double!
أصبحتِ مدينةً لي بالضعف الآن
It's your own fault for being so naive!
هذا ما اقترفته يداك بسبب سذاجتك
Here's your money!
تفضلي مالك
Wow! It's so much!
مذهل، مبلغٌ ضخم
But...
...ولكن
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
The truth is, someone else recently offered to buy my contract...
في الحقيقة، ثمة من قدّم عرضًا ضخمًا لشراء عقدي
What?!
ماذا؟
I have to hurry!
بسرعة
I need more and more money to buy her... Is there anything that I can sell?
أحتاج مزيدًا من المال، أثمة ما يمكنني بيعه هنا؟
I sold my storehouse, Komurasaki!
بعتُ متجري يا كوموراساكي
I'm so grateful...
أنا ممتنةٌ لك
Enough is enough!
طفح الكيل
I'm fed up with you!
سئمت من تصرفاتك
I'm going back to my parents' house!
سأعود إلى منزل أهلي
Do whatever you like!
افعلي ما تشائين
I'm on my way, Komurasaki!
أنا قادم يا كوموراساكي
I've even abandoned my family!
تخليت عن عائلتي
Oh no, you must think of your health...
عليك الاهتمام بصحتك
Medicine is a waste of money.
الدواء هو ضياعٌ للمال
I'll be fine.
أنا بخير
Once I get what I want, I'll be the happiest man in the world.
سأغدو أسعد رجل في العالم حالما أظفر بكِ
I admit that I dream of my life with you every single night...
أحلم كل ليلة بحلول اليوم الذي نعيش فيه معًا تحت سقف واحد-أرينسو
Oh... Komurasaki!
أجل يا كوموراساكي
I got the last of it...
جمعت المبلغ المطلوب، لم أعد أملك منزلًا
I have the final 500 gold.
هذه آخر 500 قطعة ذهبية
With this, I can buy your contract, Komurasaki!
سأتمكن من شراء عقدك بهذا المبلغ يا كوموراساكي
I'm sorry. The oiran is sick today...
المعذرة، الأويران مريضة اليوم
Oh no!
يؤسفني سماع هذا
Just be sure to give her this. I'll be back later...
احرص على تسليمها هذا، سأعود لزيارتها لاحقًا
Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي
I've come to liberate you from the pleasure hall! Come live with me!
سأحررك من منطقة الملذات، لنعش معًا من الآن فصاعدًا
You really fell for it!
فعلتها حقًّا
Way to go, you old pervert!
أحسنت أيها العجوز المنحرف
Hey, guys!
أنتم
Quit laughing and get Komurasaki for me.
كفاكم ضحكًا واستدعوا كوموراساكي
She's going to live happily ever after with me!
ستعيش معي بسعادة وهناء
You moron! Dream on!
أحمق، كفاك أوهامًا
You have enough money to liberate her?
أتملك مالًا كافيًا لعتقها؟
Of course I do! Komurasaki already has it! I asked her to keep it safe for me!
بالطبع، إنه مع كوموراساكي، فقد طلبت منها الاحتفاظ به
Oh my... It's Mr. Bingo.
عجبًا، بينغو-سان
Oh, Komurasaki! Please set things straight!
كوموراساكي، أخبريهم بالحقيقة
They're running their mouths, completely unaware of our devotion to one another!
إنهم يضحكون لجهلهم بمدى جدية علاقتنا
Oh?
عجبًا
You gave me that money, did you not?
ألم تقل إنّ ذلك المال لي؟
I've already spent it all.
أنفقته كله
But thank you.
شكرًا لك
This old coot really thought Komurasaki was in love with him!
هذا العجوز صدّق أنّ كوموراساكي-سان واقعة في حبه
What's with the old fart?
...من هذا الكهل
Komurasaki...
يا كوموراساكي؟
B-Boss Kyoshiro!
الـ-الزعيم كيوشيرو
So...
عرفتك
you're the old man who's been hanging around Komurasaki these days...
أنت العجوز الذي يضايق كوموراساكي في الآونة الأخيرة
Hanging around...? L-Let me explain!
أضايقها؟ مستحيل
Komurasaki, this is a joke, right?
كوموراساكي، ألستِ تمزحين؟
I really did sacrifice all I had!
ضحيتُ بكل ما أملك
I don't have anything left!
لم أعد أملك شيئًا
I gave it all up for you!
تخليت عن كل شيء من أجلك
Well then...
بحق
How many of these saps has it been now?
كم أصبح عدد أمثاله الآن؟
We can't have you crying out here and obstructing business, old man.
أنت تعيق عملنا بصراخك هنا أيها العجوز
If you're done, beat it!
إن انتهيت، فارحل
You lecherous old geezer!
أيها العجوز الداعر
Stop!
توقفا
I'm leaving!
سأرحل
I'm leaving, so just stop!
سأرحل حالًا
Komurasaki...!
...كوموراساكي
Komurasaki the top oiran...
...المحظية المرموقة كوموراساكي
is in procession!
تسير في موكبها
Oiran Komurasaki Wano's Top Courtesan
الأويران كوموراساكي أجمل محظية في وانو
– Lady Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي-ساما
She's stunning!
عظيمة
She's gorgeous!
جمالها يأسر الأعين
Oh, she's beautiful...!
يا لجمالها
She's radiant! My eyes!
ضيائها يعمي الأبصار
Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي
I sold my house, my family, and everything else!
بعتُ منزلي عائلتي وكل ما أملك من أجلك
Give me back my money, you thief!
أعيدي إليّ مالي أيتها اللصة
Asking for your gift back?
أتطلبون مني إعادة هداياكم؟
What a pathetic display...
أليس هذا مثيرًا للشفقة؟
To me, men are just dogs who fetch me money.
في نظري، الرجال محض كلاب يجلبون إليّ المال
If you can't do that anymore, you're dead to me.
لا قيمة لهم عندي دون مال
Gentlemen, that's as far as you go!
لن تفلتوا من قبضتنا هذه المرة
If your wallets are empty, then get lost!
إياكم إثارة المتاعب أيها المفلسون
Anyone who can't generate wealth has no place in the Flower Capital.
لا يحق للفقراء العيش في عاصمة الزهور
In the name of Shogun Orochi, we'll expel you from the city!
باسم الشوغن أوروتشي، سننفيكم من العاصمة
Please don't!
توقفوا رجاءً
The conditions outside the city are inhumane!
لا يمكننا عيش حياة كريمة خارج العاصمة
Damn! Go to hell!
...عليكِ اللعنة
Komurasaki!
يا كوموراساكي
I have nothing but scorn...
...ليس لدي سوى الازدراء
for the poor.
للفقراء-أرينسو
Open the gate!
افتحوا البوابة
Komurasaki the top oiran has arrived!
وصلت المحظية كوموراساكي
So you have a little sister, Momo?
ألديك أخت صغيرة يا مومو-كن؟
Hey, Tama!
تاما
It is rude to address me so casually! Who do you think I am?!
إنكِ تتحدثين معي بوقاحة، ألا تعلمين من أنا؟
You're Momo.
أنت مومو-كن
Forget it.
...انسي الأمر
Yes, I have a little sister.
أجل، لدي أخت صغيرة
If she is alive, she would be twenty-six.
إن كانت حية، فسيكون عمرها الآن 26 سنة
There were witnesses to my mother's death, but no one has confirmed whether Hiyori died.
ثمة شهودٌ على موت أمي، ولكن لم يشهد أحد موت هيوري
So I have faith that she is still out there!
لذا أؤمن بأنها حية في مكانٍ ما
I hope you get to see her again.
آمل أن تراها مجددًا
Well, I won't!
كلا، لا يمكنني رؤيتها بعد
If her identity were to be exposed, Orochi would target her!
إن اكتشف أوروتشي هويتها الحقيقية، فسيستهدفها لا محالة
We will reunite only when the battle is won!
لا أريد مقابلتها إلا بعد انتصارنا بالمعركة
Kozuki Momonosuke Son of Wano's Late Daimyo of Kuri
كوزكي مومونوسكي ابن دايميو كوري الراحل
You think you can show up late to work because of some gorgeous oiran, Franko?!
أتظن الانبهار بجمال الأويران سببًا وجيهًا للتأخر عن العمل يا فرانكو؟
No, Boss!
كلا يا رئيس
I'm so sorry!
أرجو المعذرة
I mean, it's hard to believe such a beauty exists!
لكنها امرأة جميلة
I know how you feel!
أتفهم شعورك يا وغد
But you know I have my reputation to uphold, you dolt!
ولكن تأخرك قد يؤثر على سمعة تجارتي أيها الأحمق
Minatomo Legendary Master Carpenter The Man Who Built Kaido's Mansion
النجار المخضرم ميناتومو الرجل الذي بنى قصر كايدو
Yes! I'm so sorry!
أجل، أرجو المعذرة
I had no intention of bringing dishonor to the name of Minatomo, the legendary master carpenter!
لم أقصد تشويه سمعة النجار المخضرم ميناتومو
Since you put in ten times the amount of work than anyone else,
بما أنك تعمل أكثر من البقية بعشرة أضعاف
I guess I don't mind if you ditch work sometimes.
فلا أمانع إن تغيّبت عن العمل أحيانًا
If you show me the plans of the Onigashima stronghold you built,
إن أريتني مخططات حصن أونيغاشيما فسأعمل بمقدار عشرة أضعاف أخرى
No! A hundred times the amount of work!
لا، بل سأعمل بمقدار مئة ضعف
Oh, yeah.
نعم تذكرت
About those Onigashima mansion blueprints you keep asking me about...
...مخططات قصر أونيغاشيما التي طالما طلبتها مني
About those... Um...
...إنها... لنرَ
Oh, this is just a tissue.
هذا مجرد منديل
About those...
...بشأن المخططات
I just remembered...
...تذكرت أمرًا
I pawned them about ten years ago!
وهو أنني رهنتها قبل عشر سنوات
Why the hell do you think I've been working for you for all these weeks?!
لأي سبب تظنني عملت تحت إمرتك بجد طوال الأسابيع الماضية؟
Ouch! Damn it, cut it out, Franko!
توقف أيها الوغد فرانكو
You attacked your master! Who do you think you are?!
كيف تجرؤ على مهاجمة ربّ عملك؟
You blockhead!
أيها النجار الأبله
You're driving me crazy!
طفح كيلي منك
Eat this!
خذ هذه
Franosuke Rocket Launcher!
قاذفات صواريخ فرانوسكي
You're fired! Get out of here, you simpleton!
كفى، أنت مطرود أيها الأحمق
Gladly! I no longer have business here anyway!
بكل سرور، فلم أعد أحتاج إلى العمل عندك
Blueprints pawned ten years ago?
رُهنت قبل 10 سنوات؟ مخططات؟
It's rare that we would ever take those...
لكننا نادرًا تردنا أشياء كهذه
Oh, maybe those!
ربما عرفت ما تقصده
What? Do you have them?!
أيعقل أنها لديك؟
Well, of course, they've long since gone to somebody else...
كلا، فقد اشتراها أحد الزبائن بالطبع
Now, who would've bought such an item...?
ولكن يصعب عليّ تذكر من اشتراها
Hmm, who was it...?
من كان يا تُرى؟
Um...
...لنرَ
Oh, yeah!
تذكرت
It was Kumagoro from the tenements. He said he'd study them. No doubt about it!
لا شك أنه كوماغورو من عقار ناغايا، قال إنه يريد دراستها
Kumagoro From the Tenements
كوماغورو من عقار ناغايا
Who?!
من هذا؟
Kumagoro From the Tenements
كوماغورو من عقار ناغايا
Who?!
من هذا؟
Kumagoro!
كوماغورو
Blueprints?
مخططات؟
Oh yeah, I had them at one point,
أجل، كانت معي فعلًا
but I fell behind on my rent, so my landlord Mr. Kobe took them.
لكنني تأخرت في دفع الإيجار وأخذها مالك العقار كوبي-سان
Kobe The Landlord
كوبي مالك العقار
Who the hell is that?
من هذا أيضًا؟
Kobe The Landlord
كوبي مالك العقار
Who the hell is that?
من هذا أيضًا؟
Kobe!
كوبي
Oh, the blueprints. They were of high quality, so I gave them to my favorite geisha.
تلك المخططات؟ كانت رائعة، لذا أعطيتها الغيشا المفضلة لدي
Miss Kisegawa.
كيسيغاوا-تشان
Do you know her?
أتعرفها؟
Kisegawa A Favored Geisha
كيسيغاوا غيشا مالك العقار المفضلة
No!
من هذه؟
Kisegawa A Favored Geisha
كيسيغاوا غيشا مالك العقار المفضلة
No!
من هذه؟
I didn't know what to do with them, so I used them as a dish mat, but then Tokijiro...
كنت استخدمها سُفرةً تحت أطباق الطعام، ثم أعطيتها توكيجيرو-سان
Okay, and who is that?
من هذا أيضًا بحق؟
Tokijiro
توكيجيرو
I had them!
كانت بحوزتي
But the Camel said they could fetch a high price and took them!
لكن راكودا-سان أخذها قائلًا إنه سيبيعها بثمن باهظ
What? "The Camel"?! An animal did?!
راكودا؟ أليس هذا حيوان؟
The Camel
راكودا
They call me the Camel!
أنا راكودا
Man, those blueprints gave me nothing but trouble!
بحق، مررتُ بوقتٍ عصيب بسبب تلك المخططات
Some guy made off with them!
ثمة رجل سرقها مني
His face was covered, but he said he came from Kuri.
كان ملثّمًا، لكنه قال إنه من مقاطعة كوري
Kuri?!
كوري؟
Um...
...عذرًا
Oh, I'm sorry. It's sea bream.
معذرةً فقد لم أنتبه إليكِ، هذه سمكة الدنيس
Is that how sea bream usually looks?
أهكذا تبدو سمكة الدنيس؟
Nice doing business with you!
شكرًا لشرائك مني
Sir Franosuke!
فرانوسكي-دونو
You seem to be in high spirits.
تبدو بخير
Of course! But what in the world are you selling?
بالطبع، لكن ما الذي تفعله؟
What? Oh, I'm peddling fish.
ماذا؟ أنا أبيع السمك
You stick out like a sore thumb! Kids are drawn to you!
إنك ملفت للأنظار، الأطفال يتجمهرون حولك
Anyway, why were you in such a hurry? Is anything the matter?
الأهم الآن، لماذا كنت مستعجلًا قبل قليل؟ أثمة مشكلة؟
Oh, yeah! Forget sticking out! We've got bigger fish to fry!
صحيح، مشكلة لفتك للأنظار لا تقارن بحجم مشكلتي
The guy I thought had the blueprints didn't have them after all!
اتضح أن من أعمل عنده لا يملك المخططات
Check the swords over there next.
تحققوا تاليًا من السيوف هناك
What?! The blueprints for Kaido's mansion are here in Kuri?!
ماذا؟ مخططات قصر كايدو موجودة هنا في مقاطعة كوري؟
Yeah! I couldn't find them even after running all over the capital!
أجل، بحثت في جميع أنحاء العاصمة ولم أجدها
I'm not sure what I should do now!
بات وجودي في العاصمة مثل عدمه
I'm sorry you had to go through that.
أعتذر لتكليفك بمهمة عقيمة
Sir Franosuke, please help the others complete their missions in the capital.
فرانوسكي-دونو، ادعم بقية المهام في العاصمة
Got it!
مفهوم
Hmm... Who would want the blueprints of Kaido's mansion?
من عساه يرغب في مخططات قصر كايدو؟
Could it be...?
...أيعقل أنه
Your Grace! Sir Kin!
دوق-ساما وكين-سان
Look at all we stole! There's food and weapons from the factory!
استطعنا سرقة أسلحة من المصنع وكثيرًا من الطعام
Nice work. Did you leave the calling card?
أحسنتم، هل تركتم الرسالة؟
We sure did!
أجل، بالطبع
But should we have?
ولكن ألا بأس بهذا؟
The note might cause the Beast Pirates to attack Ashura Doji.
بسبب الرسالة، قد يشن قراصنة الوحوش هجومًا على أشورا دوجي
That is what we want. Coming under attack will infuriate him.
هذا مبتغانا، لأنه سيغضب إن تعرض للهجوم
If we don't use his rage to goad him into fighting the Beast Pirates...
يمكننا بهذه الوسيلة حثّه على قتال قراصنة الوحوش
we'll never rekindle the fire within him.
عدا ذلك، لن يكون لديه دافع لقتالهم أبدًا
Considering the regret he's suffered for twenty years, this seems a bit heavy-handed.
تبدو وسيلة مجحفة حين أفكر بالمعاناة التي تجرّع مرارتها عشرين عام طِوَال
I know!
أعلم
But whether the means be fair or foul, we need him if we are to topple Kaido!
ولكن لا خيار آخر لدينا، فنحن نحتاج إليه لهزيمة كايدو
We need Ashura Doji's help!
نحن بحاجة إلى قوة أشورا دوجي
Hey! I'm back!
لقد عدت
Ebisu Town
بلدة إبيسو
Yasu!
ياسو-سان
Oh, you're back, Tonoyasu!
ها قد عدت يا تونوياسو
Yasu, you're back, but we still don't have any food!
ياسو-سان، أهلًا بعودتك لكننا لا نملك طعامًا لنقدّمه لك
I'm so hungry!
أنا جائع
I'm starving to death!
سأموت من شدة الجوع
How come they're so cheerful?
ما بالهم مبتهجين هكذا؟
You're quick on the uptake, mister! Everyone here looks happy, right?!
إنك دقيق الملاحظة يا سيدي، الجميع يبدون سعيدين، صحيح؟
It's slightly different from Okobore Town in Kuri.
الوضع مختلف عن بلدة أوكوبوري في مقاطعة كوري
Amongst all the species, only humans can laugh!
نحن المخلوقات الوحيدة القادرة على الضحك هكذا
Yeah!
أجل
♪ That's why you just gotta laugh! ♪
لهذا السبب علينا أن نضحك ونضحك
Pardon us!
نرجو المعذرة
– Shogun Orochi!
أوروتشي-ساما
Don't be reserved! Raise your heads!
لا داعي للرسميات، ارفعوا رؤوسكم
Now, what's for dinner?
والآن، ما قائمة العشاء الليلة؟
Yes! Everything is ready!
أمرك، كل شيء جاهز
Bring it in!
احضروا الطعام
We slaughtered the chickens we bred in the beautiful environs of Orochi Farm,
ذبحنا الدجاج الذي نربّيه في ضواحي مزرعة أوروتشي البديعة
then parboiled them...
وغليناها على نار هادئة
No! I don't feel like chicken!
كلا، لا أريد تناول الدجاج
Yes, my lord! We'll discard them!
حاضر، سنتخلص منها
Take it away!
خذوها
Next!
التالي
These fresh, delicious vegetables...
خضروات طازجة لذيذة
I don't want them!
لا أريدها
Yes, my lord! We'll throw them out!
حاضر
Next!
التالي
We present some of the finest, fattiest saury available!
سمك الإسقمري الدسم والشهي
I like saury!
أحب سمك الإسقمري
And tuna sashimi!
وساشيمي التونة
Yeah! Nothing beats tuna! Tuna!
أجل، لا ألذّ من التونة
And we have selected a variety of sake from across Wano...
جلبنا أفخم أنواع الساكي من شتّى أنحاء وانو
I get it!
فهمت
Of course you have plenty of sake to go around!
من البديهي أن تجلبوا أفخم أنواع الساكي
But how about women?
ولكن ماذا عن النساء؟
Of course, right away!
جلبنا نساء بالطبع
Good! Good!
جيد، جيد
Mom, I'm hungry!
أمي، أنا جائع
Me, too!
وأنا أيضًا
My tooth fell out from malnutrition!
سقط ضرسي من قلّة التغذية
Not like you have any food to chew anyway!
لا يوجد طعام لتمضغيه أصلًا
Now, Tonoyasu, who is this ronin fellow?
من هذا الرونين يا تونوياسو؟
He has three swords belted on!
إنه يحمل ثلاثة سيوف
You're right! Three swords!
معك حق، يحمل ثلاثة سيوف
And they're all long swords!
وجميعها سيوف طويلة
Are you trying to be funny?!
أهذا جزء من استعراض هزلي؟
Whoa, whoa! I admire this gentleman!
ويحكم، أنا معجب بحضرته
Oh no! I'm sorry to hear you've had this weirdo following you around.
عجبًا، أشفق عليك لوجود رجل غريب يتبعك أينما ذهبت أيها الرونين
Wrong! I'm the world's greatest sycophant!
أنا أعظم متملّق في العالم
Right, handsome?!
أليس كذلك أيها الفاتن؟
He sure is, but look! He has that frightful expression!
فهمت، ولكن انظر إلى ملامحه المخيفة
Come on, young man. Drop the scary look.
هيا أيها الشاب، لا تُظهر هذه الملامح المخيفة
Give us a smile!
ابتسم هكذا
Good things happen, even in a miserable hole like Ebisu!
فقد حلّ الخير على بلدة إبيسو
Wait, are you saying he paid this town a visit?!
حلّ الخير؟ أتقصدين أنّ حضرته أتى لبلدتنا؟
That's right! The Witching Hour Boy paid us another visit!
حلّ علينا الخير البارحة إذ زارنا فتى ساعة السحر
That's great!
هذا رائع
Yeah, he always comes by when we're in trouble!
أجل، يزورنا كلما اشتد بنا الجوع وتقطّعت بنا السُبل
We don't even know who he is.
إلا أنَّ لا أحد يعرف هويته
He appears at the witching hour
يظهر في ساعة السحر
and steals money from the rich, evil people of the capital...
ويسرق أموال الأثرياء الفاسدين في العاصمة
He leaves the money at poor tenements and disappears.
ثم يرميها عند أبواب منازل الفقراء ويختفي
I wonder who he is.
من يكون يا تُرى؟
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
الشكر له، الشكر له
Fortune comes to those who laugh!
الحظ يأتي لمن يضحك
So we pooled our money to ourselves a treat!
لذا اشترينا هدية لأنفسنا
Oh! What kind of treat?!
حقًّا؟ ما هذه الهدية؟
Here it is!
إنها هنا
You see?
أرأيت؟
This is it!
هذا ما اشتريناه
Please have a cup!
...اشرب هذا الكوب
You should have some, too!
يا حضرة الرونين
It's clear water!
إنها مياه نقية
We bought it with the money we were given!
اشتريناها بتلك الأموال
No, I shouldn't...
...لا، أنا
Don't worry!
لا تقلق
This water's clean, so you won't get a tummy ache!
إنها مياه نقية ولن تؤلمك معدتك إن شربتها
Yasu brought you here, so you must be a good man!
أتيت برفقة ياسو-سان، لذا لا بدّ أنك رجل لطيف
Don't be shy!
لا تخجل
Go ahead and drink! Everyone has the right to have some!
هيا اشرب يحق للجميع شرب مياه نقية
♪ Delicious water! ♪
مياه عذبة
♪ Clear water! ♪
مياه نقية
Good huh?! It seeps into every fiber of your being, right?!
أليست عذبة؟ أليست منعشة تروي العطش؟
There's that scary look again!
ها أنت مجددًا، صارت ملامحك مخيفة
Smile, or fortune won't smile on you!
ابتسم وإلا لن يبتسم الحظ لك
In this country, we call everyone's smiling face
...تسمى الوجوه البشوشة في هذه البلاد
an Ebisu grin, mister!
بـ "إبيسو غاو" يا سيدي
That's why this place is called Ebisu!
لهذا تُدعى هذه البلدة بإبيسو
We won't let poverty get us down!
لن يحبطنا الفقر
♪ Crying won't cure your poverty! ♪ ♪ So, you just gotta laugh! ♪
لن يحل البكاء معضلة فقرنا، لهذا علينا أن نضحك ونضحك
♪ You just gotta laugh! ♪
علينا أن نضحك ونضحك
Enough waiting! Let me see them!
نفد صبري، دعوني أراهن
Just a moment, my lord!
انتظر رجاءً يا مولاي
A-Are you pleased with them, my lord?
هـ-هل حاز جمالهن على رضى سعادتك؟
They're... gorgeous!
إنهن... آسرات
Simply superb! Let's start the banquet immediately!
عظيم، لنبدأ السهرة الآن
Drink!
اشربن
Dance!
ارقصن
Sing!
غنّين
Don't hold back!
لا داعي للرسميات
Kurozumi Orochi Shogun of Wano
كوروزومي أوروتشي شوغن بلاد وانو
I have arrived, my lord...
أنا هنا-أرينسو
Oh, Komurasaki! I've missed you!
يا كوموراساكي، اشتقتُ إليك
And I, you...
...وأنا أيضًا-أرينسو
my lord.
يا مولاي
Oh, y-you did?!
حـ-حقًّا؟
You did?!
حقًّا؟
Traf, what brings you here?
تراو؟ ما الذي أتى بك؟
We have an emergency. You need to hide, Black Leg.
إنها حالة طارئة، اختبئ أيها الساق السوداء-يا
This about the fight earlier? If they come back, I'll just beat them again.
هل للأمر علاقة بالشجار السابق؟ سأهزمهم إن عادوا مجددًا
That's not it.
لم أقصد ذلك
The guys that are coming know our faces!
ثمة أشخاص يعرفون وجوهنا قادمون نحونا
Is it Hawkins?
أتقصد هوكينز؟
It wouldn't be so bad if it was just him...
ليته وحده
The six strongest headliners are known as the Soaring Six.
يسمى أقوى ستة من الشينوتشي بالتوبي روبّو
Two of them are coming here.
واثنان منهم قادمان
Two?
اثنان؟
The first is Page One from the Soaring Six.
الأول هو بيج ون
Page One Soaring Six, Beast Pirates
بيج ون توبي روبو في قراصنة الوحوش
The Soaring Six... Page One...
توبي روبو؟ بيج ون؟
The other one is X Drake from the Soaring Six.
الثاني هو ديس دريك
Drake...
دريك؟
He's from the Worst Generation...
إنه من الجيل الأسوأ
Page One, why do we have to do this?
بيج ون، لماذا علينا التكفل بهذه المهمة؟
X Drake Soaring Six, Beast Pirates
ديس دريك توبي روبو في قراصنة الوحوش
To set an example, I guess...
لجعله عبرة للجميع
We've got to show them what happens when you cross the Beast Pirates in Wano.
...يجب أن يعرف من في بلاد وانو
So, why are you here...
إذًا فلماذا أنت هنا يا هوكينز؟
I'm looking for someone.
أتيت للبحث عن رجل
You'll get more than you bargained for with this job, Drake...
ستحظى بأكثر مما تريده في هذه المهمة يا دريك
Have you thought about my offer from earlier, Boss?
هل فكرت في عرضي السابق يا سيدي؟
If you're gonna break out, take me with you!
إن كنت ستهرب، فخذني معك
I'll do anything!
سأنفذ أيًّا مما تطلبه
If we join forces, we'll be unstoppable!
إن تحالفنا، فلن نهاب كائنًا من كان
Shut up already! Why don't you team up with Jaggy?!
اخرس، اذهب وتحالف مع المسنّن
You mean Kid?
أتقصد الوغد كيد؟
No way. His reputation is terrible.
كلا، فسمعته في الحضيض
Did you hear he tried to take down Big Mom?!
ألا تعلم؟ خاض قتالًا مع بيغ مام محاولًا الإطاحة بها
Rumor has it one of her subordinates— not her—took his arm,
وتفيد الإشاعات أنّ أحد أتباع بيغ مام بتر ذراعه ثم هرب يجرّ أذيال الهزيمة
Rumor? It's pathetic to listen to that kinda crap.
إشاعات؟ حالك ميؤوس منه حقًّا
Nah, I heard it from a trusted source, Boss.
لا، سمعتها من مصدر موثوق يا سيدي
Who is this source?
ومن هذا المصدر الموثوق؟
I've never tried to take down Big Mom!
أنا لم أحاول أبدًا الإطاحة ببيغ مام
K-K-K-Kid!
كـ-كـ-كـ-كيد
I wounded one of her Sweet Commanders,
أصبتُ أحد قادة الحلوى في طاقمها
took what I wanted, and left!
وأخذت مبتغاي منها وخرجت
B-B-B-But your arm...
...لـ-لـ-لـ-لكن ذراعك
I'd already lost it before that, in a battle against the Red Hair Pirates.
بُترت ذراعي قبل ذلك بمدة، في خضم معركتي مع قراصنة أحمر الشعر
Any other questions?!
هل من أسئلة أخرى؟
None.
لا
Then, let me tell you something! You listen up, too, you stupid monkey!
إذًا أصغِ إلى ما سأقوله جيدًا، وأنت كذلك أيها القرد الأحمق
What?!
ماذا؟
I'm the one who's gonna take down Kaido and get the glory!
من سيسقط كايدو وينتزع جاه المجد هو أنا
No, I am!
بل أنا
What?!
ماذا؟
Everyone, the Fire Festival is nearly upon us!
هيا هيا، اقترب موعد مهرجان النار
Let's consider this party the opening act!
لنجعل هذه الحفلة افتتاحية
Go ahead and indulge yourselves!
هيا استمتعوا
This is Wano!
فهذه بلاد وانو
We may as well be in heaven!
لا تظنوا أنّها الجنة
Eat and drink to your heart's content!
كلوا حتى التخمة واشربوا حتى الثمالة
They're approaching from the southeast in a massive ship!
ثمة سفينة ضخمة تقترب الآن من الجنوب الشرقي
She actually came!
إذًا فأتت حقًّا
Blast them!
اغرقوها في البحر
Don't let her enter the country!
إياكم أن تدخل البلاد
But there is a problem...
...ولكن ثمة مشكلة
Carp are pulling their ship and they're charing ahead!
إنهم يتقدمون بسرعة بفضل جر أسماك الشبوط لسفينتهم
What?!
ماذا؟
How do they know how to climb the waterfall?!
أنّى لهم معرفة كيفية صعود الشلال؟
Well, the Big Mom Pirates are known for gathering good intel.
هذا لأن قراصنة بيغ مام لديهم الكفاءة بجمع المعلومات
Shut it! I don't care!
اخرس، لا يهمني ذلك
We knew they were coming!
كنا نعلم أنهم قادمون
Just sink them already!
اغرقوهم حالًا
That old bag! I'm sure she remembers that I warned her...
تلك العجوز الشمطاء، متأكد أنها تتذكر تحذيري لها
I'll kill you if you come here, Linlin!
سأقتلكِ إن أتيتِ يا لينلين
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat...
لن تفلت مني يا قبعة القش